<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>technology on blog</title>
    <link>https://daosyn.info/blog/categories/technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in technology on blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 00:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://daosyn.info/blog/categories/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>switching terminal focus with chunkwm</title>
      <link>https://daosyn.info/blog/posts/focus-chunkwm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daosyn.info/blog/posts/focus-chunkwm/</guid>
      <description>A quick little trick I solved for recently was switching between multiple iTerm2 windows that I would have open during a normal work day.
My workflow consists of using chunkwm across three different desktops to manage all of my windows without much effort on my part:
 Desktop 1 (left) is solely for my terminal windows, which are tiled. Desktop 2 (center) contains my web browser and any other non-IDE tool/app that I may need to use, in monocle format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSP Go</title>
      <link>https://daosyn.info/blog/posts/psp-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daosyn.info/blog/posts/psp-go/</guid>
      <description>Coincidentally or not, I have been thoroughly obsessed with all things &amp;ldquo;Go&amp;rdquo; lately&amp;hellip;
I remember back in 2009 when the PSP Go was first released. Being a jobless high schooler at the time, I gawked at the release price of 249 USD, clamoring as to why anyone would spend that much money for a gimped PSP; that is, the PSP Go was smaller, used a proprietary charging/USB cable and memory card, and lacked the UMD drive that was used for physical copies of its game software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Circling Back - Yubikey Setup With Surface Go</title>
      <link>https://daosyn.info/blog/posts/circling-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daosyn.info/blog/posts/circling-back/</guid>
      <description>A small hurdle that I have been running into recently has been setting up my Yubikey with all of the devices that I use.
The Yubikey has been in my possession for a few months now. I started using only the U2F feature with popular services such as Google, Twitter, Facebook, and GitHub, and it was quick and painless to get it set up and running. I recently found out that my workplace also supports Yubikeys for multi-factor authentication, even though only the one-time password feature is supported.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go[lang] and [Surface] Go</title>
      <link>https://daosyn.info/blog/posts/go-and-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daosyn.info/blog/posts/go-and-go/</guid>
      <description>I am currently learning Go on the side for fun. I really appreciate the conciseness of every facet of the language, from its built-in testing package, a formatter that standardizes coding style, an enforced but sensible workspace structure, and the sheer simplicity of the language&amp;rsquo;s syntax.
Recently, I unintentionally obtained a Surface Go for myself. I had purchased one online for my younger sister, but since it did not arrive in time, I grabbed another one from a physical store.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>