<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on daosyn</title>
    <link>https://daosyn.info/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on daosyn</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 20:22:37 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://daosyn.info/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>switching terminal focus with chunkwm</title>
      <link>https://daosyn.info/post/focus-chunkwm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 20:22:37 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daosyn.info/post/focus-chunkwm/</guid>
      <description>A quick little trick I solved for recently was switching between multiple iTerm2 windows that I would have open during a normal work day. My workflow consists of using chunkwm across three different desktops to manage all of my windows without much effort on my part:
 Desktop 1 (left) is solely for my terminal windows, which are tiled. Desktop 2 (center) contains my web browser and any other non-IDE tool/app that I may need to use, in monocle format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSP Go</title>
      <link>https://daosyn.info/post/psp-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 11:03:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daosyn.info/post/psp-go/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Coincidentally or not, I have been thoroughly obsessed with all things &amp;ldquo;Go&amp;rdquo; lately&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remember back in 2009 when the PSP Go was first released.
Being a jobless high schooler at the time, I gawked at the release price of 249 USD, clamoring as to why anyone would spend that much money for a gimped PSP; that is, the PSP Go was smaller, used a proprietary charging/USB cable and memory card, and lacked the UMD drive that was used for physical copies of its game software.
Digital software was still a budding prospect at the time, with what is now a convenience being a slight inconvenience back then.
Memory cards were still fairly expensive and limited, and the PSP Go was fitted with an older wireless standard that was outdated before it even hit the shelves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why would the PSP Go be any good today, in 2018, when technology has advanced even further and the tiny device is now practically an antique?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The answer is that exploitation takes time.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Circling Back - Yubikey Setup With Surface Go</title>
      <link>https://daosyn.info/post/circling-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 06:46:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daosyn.info/post/circling-back/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A small hurdle that I have been running into recently has been setting up my Yubikey with all of the devices that I use.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go[lang] and [Surface] Go</title>
      <link>https://daosyn.info/post/go-and-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 17:25:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daosyn.info/post/go-and-go/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am currently learning Go on the side for fun.
I really appreciate the conciseness of every facet of the language, from its built-in testing package, a formatter that standardizes coding style, an enforced but sensible workspace structure, and the sheer simplicity of the language&amp;rsquo;s syntax.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>