<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Naivety on daosyn.info</title>
    <link>https://daosyn.info/categories/naivety/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Naivety on daosyn.info</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://daosyn.info/categories/naivety/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>dating</title>
      <link>https://daosyn.info/posts/dating/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daosyn.info/posts/dating/</guid>
      <description>Relationships have the potential to be so satiating at times but also draining at others. We tug at each other&amp;rsquo;s emotional chords until they are right on the verge of snapping, and then decide at that moment whether to rip it apart quickly like some sort of adhesive putty or to give it a moment to rest, like a freshly stretched out piece of taffy. They need time to breath and relax, but also conversely if they fail to &amp;ldquo;work out&amp;rdquo; the relationship could just as likely fizzle out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>surfing</title>
      <link>https://daosyn.info/posts/surfing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daosyn.info/posts/surfing/</guid>
      <description>&amp;hellip;no, not the act of riding on a rushing wave of water &amp;ndash; the indoor kind, channel surfing. What I had thought was a lost art in the age of Netflix and the Internet has actually never been so prevalent. It has just taken on a different form, with people constantly swiping through apps on their phones, from Instagram to Facebook, from Reddit to Google, from Gmail to Discord, repeat. Even within apps, people find themselves engrossed in switching from the feed to a specific profile or more focused view, and then switching back again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>best</title>
      <link>https://daosyn.info/posts/best/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daosyn.info/posts/best/</guid>
      <description>I want to be good at everything but not necessarily the best at everything.
Why is that?
Being the best at everything is hard work. From just a sheer numbers game, it is almost impossible to become the best at something. And once one becomes the best, the next person in line is always ready to take the spot. It takes a lot of effort to get to the spot, but it takes even more effort to maintain that spot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>velleity</title>
      <link>https://daosyn.info/posts/velleity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daosyn.info/posts/velleity/</guid>
      <description>Everyone has inclinations to do things. Everyone has ideas. Ideas are cheap. Ideas are easy to make. Not everyone has the intensity of desire to act upon these ideas and thoughts, however. A person can sit in an office at a corporate job and be ordered to create things on behalf of the company and the person will do them because there is this necessity to do so, because money is a tangible reward and because money is essential to living in society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>choices</title>
      <link>https://daosyn.info/posts/choices/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://daosyn.info/posts/choices/</guid>
      <description>It would seem that in this day and age of the Internet, people can constantly find themselves something to do to occupy their purposeless but satisfying lives in this world. However, it is quite the opposite. There is simply an overabundance of options which causes one to become totally uncertain whether one option is a better choice than the other. It becomes so easy to get lost in that metaphorical fig tree that the main character describes in The Bell Jar.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>